<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LongPressPopupSample</string>
    <string name="cupcacke">Cupcake</string>
    <string name="donut">Donut</string>
    <string name="eclair">Eclair</string>
    <string name="froyo">Froyo</string>
    <string name="ice_cream_sandwich">Ice Cream Sandwich</string>
    <string name="gingerbread">Gingerbread</string>
    <string name="honeycomb">Honeycomb</string>
    <string name="jelly_bean">Jelly Bean</string>
    <string name="kit_kat">KitKat</string>
    <string name="lollipop">Lollipop</string>
    <string name="marshmellow">Marshmellow</string>
    <string name="nougat">Noutgat</string>
    <string name="cupcacke_desc">Android 1.5 \'Cupcake\' was the second Android version developed by
        Google, a major platform release deployable to Android-powered handsets starting
        in May 2009. The release includes new features for users and developers, as well as
        changes in the Android framework API. For developers, the Android 1.5 platform is
        available as a downloadable component for the Android SDK.

        Android 1.5 included new features such as an on-screen keyboard and Bluetooth support as
        well as improvements to existing features such as UI changes for application management and
        several Google apps.</string>
    <string name="donut_desc">Android 1.6 \'Donut\' is a discontinued version and the dessert-themed
        Android code name for the version 1.6 update of the open source Android mobile operating
        system. Developed by Google, Donut made its debut in fall 2009 for a variety of smartphones,
        adding new features like support for CDMA smartphones, support for additional screen sizes,
        a battery usage indicator, and a text-to-speech engine.</string>
    <string name="eclair_desc">Android 2.0–2.1 \'Eclair\' is a discontinued version of the Android
        mobile operating system developed by Google. Unveiled on October 26, 2009,
        Android 2.1 builds upon the significant changes made in Android 1.6 \'Donut\'.\n
        User experience:
        The default home screen of Eclair displays a persistent Google Search bar across the top
        of the screen. The camera app was also redesigned with numerous new camera features,
        including flash support, digital zoom, scene mode, white balance,
        color effect and macro focus. The photo gallery app also contains basic photo editing tools.
        Addition of live wallpapers, allowing the animation of home-screen background images
        to show movement. Speech-to-text was first introduced, replacing the comma key.

        Platform
        Android Eclair inherits platform additions from the Donut release, and also adds support
        for near-field communication (NFC), ability to search all saved SMS and MMS messages,
        improved Google Maps 3.1.2, and Exchange support for the Email app.
        The operating system also provides improved typing speed on virtual keyboard,
        along with new accessibility, calendar, and virtual private network APIs.
        For internet browsing, Android Eclair also adds support for HTML5, refreshed
        browser UI with bookmark thumbnails and double-tap zoom.</string>
    <string name="froyo_desc">Android 2.2–2.2.3 \'Froyo\' is a discontinued version of the
        Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions
        between 2.2 and 2.2.3. It was unveiled on May 20, 2010,
        during the Google I/O 2010 conference.

        One of the most prominent changes in the Froyo release was USB tethering and Wi-Fi hotspot
        functionality. Other changes include support for the
        Android Cloud to Device Messaging (C2DM) service, enabling push notifications,
        Additional application speed improvements, implemented through JIT compilation and
        displayed within applications as top-of-the-screen banners.

        As of August 13, 2016, statistics issued by Google indicate that 0.1% of all
        Android devices accessing Google Play run Froyo.</string>
    <string name="gingerbread_desc">Android 2.3–2.3.7 \'Gingerbread\' is a discontinued version of
        the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and released in December 2010.
        The Gingerbread release introduced support for near field communication (NFC)—used in
        mobile payment solutions—and Session Initiation Protocol (SIP)—used
        in VoIP internet telephony.

        Gingerbread\'s user interface was refined in many ways, making it easier to master,
        faster to use, and more power-efficient. A simplified color scheme with a black
        background gave vividness and contrast to the notification bar, menus, and other user
        interface components. Improvements in menus and settings resulted in easier navigation
        and system control.

        The Nexus S smartphone, released in 2010, was the first phone from the Google Nexus line
        that ran Gingerbread, and also the first one from the line with built-in NFC functionality.

        Gingerbread uses version 2.6.35 of the Linux kernel.

        As of September 5, 2016, statistics issued by Google indicate that 1.5% of all
        Android devices accessing Google Play run Gingerbread.</string>
    <string name="honeycomb_desc">Android 3.0–3.2.6 \'Honeycomb\' is a discontinued version of the
        Android platform that was designed for devices with larger screen sizes, particularly
        tablets. Honeycomb debuted with the Motorola Xoom in February 2011. Besides the addition
        of new features, Honeycomb introduced a new so-called \'holographic\' user interface theme
        and an interaction model that built on the main features of Android, such as multitasking,
        notifications and widgets.</string>
    <string name="ice_cream_sandwich_desc"><!--Android 4.0–4.0.4 Ice Cream Sandwich is a
        discontinued version of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google.
        Unveiled on October 19, 2011, Android 4.0 builds upon the significant changes made by the
        tablet-only release Android Honeycomb, in an effort to create a unified platform for both
        smartphones and tablets, whilst simplifying and modernizing the overall Android experience
        around a new set of human interface guidelines. As part of these efforts, Android 4.0
        introduced a new visual appearance codenamed \'Holo\', which is built around a cleaner,
        minimalist design, and a new default typeface named Roboto.

        The Ice Cream Sandwich release also introduced a number of other new features,
        including a refreshed home screen, near-field communication (NFC) support and the
        ability to \'beam\' content to another user using the technology, an updated web browser,
        a new contacts manager with social network integration, the ability to access the camera
        and control music playback from the lock screen, visual voicemail support, face recognition
        for device unlocking (\'Face Unlock\'), the ability to monitor and limit mobile data usage,
        and other internal improvements.

        Android 4.0 received positive reviews by critics, who praised the cleaner,
        revamped appearance of the operating system in comparison to previous versions,
        along with its improved performance and functionality. However, critics still felt
        that some of Android 4.0\'s stock apps were still lacking in quality and functionality in
        comparison to third-party equivalents, and regarded some of the operating system's new
        features, particularly the \'face unlock\' feature, as being gimmicks.--></string>
    <string name="jelly_bean_desc">Android 4.1–4.3.1 \'Jelly Bean\' is the name given to three major
        point releases of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning
        versions between 4.1 and 4.3.1.

        The first of these three, 4.1, was unveiled at Google\'s I/O developer conference in
        June 2012, focusing on performance improvements designed to give the operating
        system a smoother and more responsive feel, improvements to the notification system
        allowing for \"expandable\" notifications with action buttons, and other internal changes.
        Two more releases were made under the Jelly Bean name in October 2012 and July 2013
        respectively, including 4.2—which included further optimizations, multi-user support for
        tablets, lock screen widgets, quick settings, and screen savers, and 4.3—contained
        further improvements and updates to the underlying Android platform.</string>
    <string name="kit_kat_desc">Android 4.4–4.4.4 \'KitKat\' is a version of the Android mobile
        operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 4.4 and 4.4.4.
        Unveiled on September 3, 2013, KitKat focused primarily on optimizing the operating system
        for improved performance on entry-level devices with limited resources.</string>
    <string name="lollipop_desc">Android 5.0–5.1.1 \'Lollipop\' is a version of the Android mobile
        operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 5.0 and 5.1.1.
        Unveiled on June 25, 2014 at the Google I/O 2014 conference, it became available through
        official over-the-air (OTA) updates on November 12, 2014, for select devices that run
        distributions of Android serviced by Google (such as Nexus and Google Play edition devices).
        Its source code was made available on November 3, 2014.

        One of the most prominent changes in the Lollipop release is a redesigned user interface
        built around a design language known as Material Design, which was made to retain a
        paper-like feel to the interface. Other changes include improvements to the notifications,
        which can be accessed from the lockscreen and displayed within applications as
        top-of-the-screen banners. Google also made internal changes to the platform, with the
        Android Runtime (ART) officially replacing Dalvik for improved application performance,
        and with changes intended to improve and optimize battery usage.

        As of November 2016, statistics issued by Google indicate that 34% of all Android devices
        accessing Google Play run Lollipop.</string>
    <string name="marshmellow_desc">Android 6.0–6.0.1 \'Marshmallow\'
        (codenamed M during development)is the 6th major version of the Android operating system.
        First unveiled in May 2015 at Google I/O, it was officially released in October 2015.

        Marshmallow primarily focuses on improving the overall user experience of Lollipop,
        introducing a new permissions architecture, new APIs for contextual assistants
        (a feature notably leveraged by \'Now On Tap\'—a new capability of the Google searching
        by contextualizing an app into a simpler interface by Google Now), a new power management
        system that reduces background activity when a device is not being physically handled,
        native support for fingerprint recognition and USB Type-C connectors, the ability to
        migrate data and applications to a microSD card and use it as primary storage,
        and other internal changes.

        As of September 2016, 18.7% of devices accessing Google Play run Android 6.0</string>
    <string name="nougat_desc">Android 7.0-7.1 \'Nougat\' (codenamed Android N during development)
        is the seventh major version of the Android operating system.
        First released as a beta build on March 9, 2016, it was officially released on August 22,
        2016, with Nexus devices being the first to receive the update.

        Nougat introduces notable changes to the operating system and its development platform,
        including the ability to display multiple apps on-screen at once in a split-screen view,
        support for inline replies to notifications, as well as an OpenJDK-based Java environment
        and support for the Vulkan graphics rendering API, and \'seamless\' system updates on
        supported devices.</string>
    <string name="cupcacke_numbers">1.5</string>
    <string name="donut_numbers">1.6</string>
    <string name="eclair_numbers">2.0 – 2.1</string>
    <string name="froyo_numbers">2.2 – 2.2.3</string>
    <string name="gingerbread_numbers">2.3 – 2.3.7</string>
    <string name="honeycomb_numbers">3.0 – 3.2.6</string>
    <string name="ice_cream_sandwich_numbers">4.0 – 4.0.3</string>
    <string name="jelly_bean_numbers">4.1 – 4.3.1</string>
    <string name="kit_kat_numbers">4.4 – 4.4.4</string>
    <string name="lollipop_numbers">5.0 – 5.1.1</string>
    <string name="marshmellow_numbers">6.0 – 6.0.1</string>
    <string name="nougat_numbers">7.0 – 7.1</string>
    <string name="my_github">My GitHub</string>
    <string name="my_github_url">https://github.com/RiccardoMoro</string>
</resources>
